[{"id":0,"question":"4/4","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":1,"question":"5/5","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"question":"9/9","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"question":"6/1","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"question":"6/3","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":5,"question":"5/1","choices":[4,5,6],"rightAnswer":5,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":6,"question":"9/1","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":7,"question":"6/1","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":8,"question":"3/1","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":9,"question":"6/2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":10,"question":"5/1","choices":[4,5,6],"rightAnswer":5,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":11,"question":"6/3","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":12,"question":"4/4","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":13,"question":"6/3","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":14,"question":"1/1","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":15,"question":"8/8","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":16,"question":"6/2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":17,"question":"6/2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":18,"question":"9/3","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":19,"question":"8/2","choices":[3,4,5],"rightAnswer":4,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":20,"question":"74/2","choices":[36,37,38],"rightAnswer":37,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":21,"question":"54/2","choices":[26,27,28],"rightAnswer":27,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":22,"question":"88/4","choices":[21,22,23],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":23,"question":"74/2","choices":[36,37,38],"rightAnswer":37,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":24,"question":"64/4","choices":[15,16,17],"rightAnswer":16,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":25,"question":"96/6","choices":[15,16,17],"rightAnswer":16,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":26,"question":"93/3","choices":[30,31,32],"rightAnswer":31,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":27,"question":"56/4","choices":[13,14,15],"rightAnswer":14,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":28,"question":"42/3","choices":[13,14,15],"rightAnswer":14,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":29,"question":"12/6","choices":[1,2,3],"rightAnswer":2,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":30,"question":"18/2","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":31,"question":"48/6","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":32,"question":"56/7","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":33,"question":"36/3","choices":[11,12,13],"rightAnswer":12,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":34,"question":"72/9","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":35,"question":"91/7","choices":[12,13,14],"rightAnswer":13,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":36,"question":"63/9","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":37,"question":"54/9","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":38,"question":"34/2","choices":[16,17,18],"rightAnswer":17,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":39,"question":"40/4","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":40,"question":"196/4","choices":[48,49,50],"rightAnswer":49,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":41,"question":"452/2","choices":[225,226,227],"rightAnswer":226,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":42,"question":"870/3","choices":[289,290,291],"rightAnswer":290,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":43,"question":"405/5","choices":[80,81,82],"rightAnswer":81,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":44,"question":"220/4","choices":[54,55,56],"rightAnswer":55,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":45,"question":"832/8","choices":[103,104,105],"rightAnswer":104,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":46,"question":"170/5","choices":[33,34,35],"rightAnswer":34,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":47,"question":"674/2","choices":[336,337,338],"rightAnswer":337,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":48,"question":"925/5","choices":[184,185,186],"rightAnswer":185,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":49,"question":"990/9","choices":[109,110,111],"rightAnswer":110,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":50,"question":"286/2","choices":[142,143,144],"rightAnswer":143,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":51,"question":"663/3","choices":[220,221,222],"rightAnswer":221,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":52,"question":"894/6","choices":[148,149,150],"rightAnswer":149,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"354/6","choices":[58,59,60],"rightAnswer":59,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":54,"question":"476/7","choices":[67,68,69],"rightAnswer":68,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":55,"question":"548/2","choices":[273,274,275],"rightAnswer":274,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":56,"question":"132/2","choices":[65,66,67],"rightAnswer":66,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":57,"question":"555/3","choices":[184,185,186],"rightAnswer":185,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":58,"question":"992/8","choices":[123,124,125],"rightAnswer":124,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"600/8","choices":[74,75,76],"rightAnswer":75,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":60,"question":"760/76","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":61,"question":"680/68","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":62,"question":"817/19","choices":[42,43,44],"rightAnswer":43,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":63,"question":"900/30","choices":[29,30,31],"rightAnswer":30,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":64,"question":"621/27","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":65,"question":"350/50","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":66,"question":"232/29","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":67,"question":"414/18","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"200/25","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":69,"question":"636/12","choices":[52,53,54],"rightAnswer":53,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":70,"question":"559/43","choices":[12,13,14],"rightAnswer":13,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":71,"question":"988/13","choices":[75,76,77],"rightAnswer":76,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"255/15","choices":[16,17,18],"rightAnswer":17,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":73,"question":"528/11","choices":[47,48,49],"rightAnswer":48,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":74,"question":"420/12","choices":[34,35,36],"rightAnswer":35,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":75,"question":"725/29","choices":[24,25,26],"rightAnswer":25,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":76,"question":"672/12","choices":[55,56,57],"rightAnswer":56,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":77,"question":"286/22","choices":[12,13,14],"rightAnswer":13,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"855/19","choices":[44,45,46],"rightAnswer":45,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"250/25","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":80,"question":"4692/17","choices":[275,276,277],"rightAnswer":276,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":81,"question":"7194/22","choices":[326,327,328],"rightAnswer":327,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":82,"question":"3354/26","choices":[128,129,130],"rightAnswer":129,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":83,"question":"8547/21","choices":[406,407,408],"rightAnswer":407,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":84,"question":"5740/28","choices":[204,205,206],"rightAnswer":205,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":85,"question":"3731/13","choices":[286,287,288],"rightAnswer":287,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":86,"question":"9477/81","choices":[116,117,118],"rightAnswer":117,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":87,"question":"5238/18","choices":[290,291,292],"rightAnswer":291,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":88,"question":"3770/13","choices":[289,290,291],"rightAnswer":290,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":89,"question":"3182/74","choices":[42,43,44],"rightAnswer":43,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":90,"question":"4180/19","choices":[219,220,221],"rightAnswer":220,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"2610/18","choices":[144,145,146],"rightAnswer":145,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":92,"question":"6574/38","choices":[172,173,174],"rightAnswer":173,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":93,"question":"1335/15","choices":[88,89,90],"rightAnswer":89,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":94,"question":"7866/18","choices":[436,437,438],"rightAnswer":437,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"6300/45","choices":[139,140,141],"rightAnswer":140,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":96,"question":"8084/47","choices":[171,172,173],"rightAnswer":172,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":97,"question":"8466/51","choices":[165,166,167],"rightAnswer":166,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":98,"question":"3795/15","choices":[252,253,254],"rightAnswer":253,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":99,"question":"5640/47","choices":[119,120,121],"rightAnswer":120,"qOperator":"/","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false}]